The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Give me a break.
Scram !
Ceng Niu !?
You're still alive !?
Ceng Niu ?
Why does he have such an overbearing aura ?
This aura
is something only ancient cultivators could possess.
No...
You're not him !
Who the hell are you ?!
I'm asking you,
which generation Suzaku are you ?
The 14th generation Suzaku.
On the behalf of Ye Wuyou,
this old man won't kill you today.
Now scram !
You...
How do you know the name of the first Suzaku ?
Ye Wuyou ?
Only Suzaku successors
know that name.
An outsiders couldn't possibly know...
His attitude is so overbearing...
Could he be !?
Greetings, Ancestor.
Junior is leaving.
Leave the 4th soul !
Forget it,
you need the 4th soul against the Forsaken Immortal Clan.
Ye Wuyou once saved me
so I'll lend it for 3 years.
Thank you, Ancestor.
But...
However...
Since you guessed my identity,
then you must know my rules.
Are you
just leaving like this !?
Junior was negligent.
are 2 fingers enough ?
Leave another one.
Now scram.
Ceng Niu !
Possession ?!
Senior, stop !
Little brat, you were about to make a mistake.
If this old man had his old temper,
I would have killed you instantly !
Who said you could rain !?
Now scatter for me !
This...
What's going on ?
Why did you ask for the 4th soul !?
If that brat had noticed something,
I would've had to go back to sleep just after waking up !
The 4th soul can wait until I get a new body
and restore my cultivation.
I'll storm Mount Suzaku and take it back !
May I ask who Senior is ?
Wang Lin,
can you tell that brat
who I am.
He's Situ Nan.
Situ Nan ?
2nd generation Suzaku.
No wonder the Suzaku fled...
Junior Du Tian of the Soul Refining Sect
greets Senior.
During the previous war,
your 4th ancestor helped us.
Since you helped Wang Lin to reach Soul Transformation
and wake me up,
Little brat,
although your lifespan is ending,
I promise you
that when I recover my cultivation,
I'll reclaim your 4th ancestor's soul
and restore the Soul Refining Sect.
Senior Brother,
your prediction worked...
The clouds and the mist cannot hide a thousand mountains.
I will not become a sinner of our sect.
This wish has remained unchanged for thousands of years.
I can face you with pride now,
and our master,
The Dao can be condensed into a single thought.
and all of the Ancestors.
The past flashes before my eyes
as I turn around to let it go.
Little friend Ceng Niu,
this old man has one last request.
Resolutely carrying the torch forward.
I will condense my memory
inside the Soul Flag.
Keep it safe for me
and let future disciples see
Even though the cycle of reincarnation is endless,
I have no regrets in my heart.
how glorious our Soul Refining Sect once was.
Only when facing death
does one realize they have no regrets.
I will fulfill your wish,\NI will rush forward through dust and smoke to chase the light.
Even if the road is difficult,\NI will give it my heart and soul.
Father !
Mother !
Du Tian\NKid
Behind you, countless clear eyes\Nlook at the world you made.
You soul will not die,\Nit will live forever.
Kid,
are you willing to come with me ?
Yun Yimo\NFormer Soul Refining Sect Leader\NLate stage Soul Transformation
Du Tian\NAdult
I, Du Tian,
swear to devote this life
to protecting our sect !
I will dare to rely on the Billion-Soul Flag
to face the wind and stirr up a storm.
I'm betting on how dazzling\Nthis single spark can become.
I have witnessed the vicissitudes of life
and travelled through this long night but I remain untainted.
The promise I once broke
was just reignited.
Master...
Master,
I've fulfilled my promise.
I hold in my heart
your wish to see your past glory once more.
Kid,
There will always be someone
to see the world you protected.
are you willing to come with me ?
Even if it takes countless lifetimes.
Seeing mountains and rivers is like meeting people.
Let me carry on all the wishes
I, Du Tian,
will now wipe my consciousness
that you couldn't fulfill.
and become a soul fragment of the Soul Flag !
Master...
disciple...
is coming.
Senior, rest assured.
I will fulfill my promise
to the Soul Refining Sect.
North of the\NSuzaku Continent
We must attack
and destroy this Reincarnation Tree !
At least the Suzaku
Fourth Ancestor of the\NForsaken Immortal Clan\N9-Leaf Shaman
was able to fight me.
But you
are merely Early stage Ascendant !
The battle has already started.
This tree was nurtured by Ancestral Spirits.
I remember that Ye Wuyou
studied a technique
to absorb their power
to increase your cultivation.
I like this northern one.
Senior !
What are you doing !?
Do you really think
that the Forsaken Immortal Clan wouldn't be prepared ?
Forsaken Immortal Clan,
formation !
Formation,
activate !
Retreat !
Are you trying to leave now ?
It's too late !
Fight to the death !
Fight !
What's wrong ?
What happened ?
It stopped ?
This tastes awful !
Our Ancestral Spirit cultivated for thousands of years
and you ate it !
You bastard !
I'll kill you !
Don't just stand there,
hurry up !
Retreat !
Quick !
Go !
Brat, I'm here !
Catch me if you can !
Stay right there !
Devouring Ancestral Spirits restores cultivation
and eliminates the Warriors
the Forsaken Immortal Clan were incubating.
A worthy tribute to the first Suzaku !
What will you do now ?
I'll find a body that matches my Spirit Root.
Once I'm back at my prime,
I'll hunt down those people one by one !
And if they're dead,
their descendants will pay for their crimes !
Senior,
I know the Heaven Defying Bead
is a heavenly artifact
that surpasses even celestial artifacts.
Since it has fused with my soul
I don't know if I can return it to you.
Nonsense !
That damned bead ruined me,
I don't want it.
You can keep it.
Situ...
What ?
Thank you.
Wh..
Why are you so sentimental ?
Since I watched you grow,
you're like my disciple.
It's just a stupid bead,
you don't need to say that.
It makes me sick.
What's so funny !?
If you want to thank me
then find me a suitable body.
The Suzaku has a disciple named Qian Feng.
His body might do the trick.
The Suzaku's disciple...
Nevermind,
since the first Suzaku helped me,
I'll find another.
Interesting...
How can such a body exist ?
Once possessed,
it will match its Spirit Root.
It's a body made to be possessed.
It's this one !
Little Lin,
let's lure him to the Northern Flame Plains.
Little Tattoo kid,
grandpa is here !
Northern Flame Plains
Little Tattoo kid,
How many times did I have to stop to wait for you ?
You must hurry up !
His repeated provocations
are suspicious...
But if he hasn't refined the spirit
I can still reclaim it !
It's him !
Is this...
a restriction ?
The Nine-Li Fog
is a natural formation.
Little Lin,
you will use it
to trap that Ascendant brat.
Extreme Flame Blood Light ?
this light causes any creature with blood
to burn, boil and die
within 10 breaths !
Pathetic tricks !
Give me the Ancestral Spirit !
You dare to possess me !?
Get out !
Do it now !
Seal !
Well done.
With this demon child's body, an Ascendant cultivator
and the Ancestral Spirit
it won't take long
for me to fully recover.
I'll come and find you then.
You don't need me to guard you ?
You don't need to.
The Nine-Li Fog will protect me.
By the way,
I've been meaning to ask you.
I've never heard of a Ji Realm cultivator above Nascent Soul
but you somehow are Soul Transformation.
How did you do it ?
I extracted the Ji Realm.
Resisting its temptation
and extracting it
is remarkable.
However,
I've heard there is another method.
If you obtain and refine
a Cultivation Planet Crystal
you can breakthrough that Ji Realm bottleneck.
I'm not sure if it can help Ji Realm cultivators
to breakthrough.
But if you want to leave planet Suzaku
you will need it anyways.
What do you mean ?
Before I became the Suzaku
I thought it was a powerful artifact.
But then, I learned that
it is how rank 6 cultivation countries
control their planet.
The Cultivation Alliance creates these crystals
and when a country reaches rank 6
they're given a planet
and a Cultivation Planet Crystal.
Once it's activated,
all lifeforms born on that planet
will have a strand of their soul stolen by the crystal.
There is an item called the Cultivation Planet Heart.
It's held by the successive generations of Suzakus.
By using a bit of lifespan,
they can kill anyone whose soul strand is inside it.
During your Ascendant breakthrough,
you can extract it.
There is no way around it.
When I learned of this,
I secretly sealed our Cultivation Planet Crystal.
Although it still absorbs soul strands,
the seal prevents
anyone from controlling it.
This is why planet Suzaku is in such a mess.
If Zhuque Zi breaks the seal,
it will be a disaster.
Enough,
let's talk about it once I recover.
You don’t need to worry too much,
I’m still here.
Cultivation Planet Crystal...
I, Wang Lin,
will never leave my life in someone's hands.
As for Wan'er's soul strand...
I need to recover it too !
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.